dreamcss.com 2012-05-07

# Privacy Policy

Posted by **ravindra** **Jan 3, 2009**

This is the privacy policy of **Dreamcss.com**  
 **Dreamcss.com** does not engage in the collection, distribution, sale or use of personally identifiable information about web users, such as name, phone number and street address. **Dreamcss.com** does not conduct individual web user “profiling”.  
 **Email** :  
Email address mentioned in the comment form will always be use for privacy and never be used for spamming. Though I highly recommend never post your Email into the comments, so that other can’t see it.  
 **Comments** :  
We love comments, but any comments which is abusive, spread hatred, racial or any way hurting anyone opinion will never be entertained. We keep our comments moderated to maintain the integrity of individuals.  
 **Cookies :**  
With respect to cookies, we do place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is the information you supply yourself. **Dreamcss.com** uses cookies to track user traffic patterns and our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. Besides, third parties ad server companies may also be placing and reading cookies in your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on **Dreamcss.com**. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site.  
 **Third Party Advertisements :**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>  
**External Links :**  
With regards to outside links, this website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that **Dreamcss.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

"Hi Burst! I confirm that I own the domain [http://dreamcss.com](http://dreamcss.com/), and I own and control all content herein."
